["Speaking Out" playing]
♪ If I could read your mind
I'd tell you... ♪
[mom] My baby girl
is the sweetest, kindest human.
But she's been hurt in the past
really bad.
I tell her all the time
that you've got to let your guard down.
♪ Every time I say I want you
I want you ♪
♪ Every time I say I need you
I need you... ♪
[sister]
My sister would like to have somebody
that can listen and can understand her.
You know, the good and the bad.
Somebody that gets her crazy side
that she has.
♪ Every time I say I want you
I want you ♪
♪ Every time I say I need you
I need you ♪
♪ I can feel you even closer now
that we are speaking out... ♪
[woman] Most men want Heather
because of her looks,
but she's so much more than that.
[sister]
I feel like she does want a companion,
'cause she has been alone for so long.
She wants a partner eventually.
You know, who doesn't?
♪ All the time when I was lonely, lonely ♪
♪ All the days that you were
Hungry, hungry ♪
♪ I can feel my heart is younger now
That we are speaking out ♪
[Ernesto chuckles]
Heather, right?
Hello, handsome.
-Hi.
-Yes, I'm Heather.
-I'm Ernesto. Nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you.
-How are you tonight?
-I'm doing great.
-I love your dress. It's beautiful.
-Why, thank you.
I love the rasp of your voice, too.
You look very dapper.
-Thank you.
-Do you want to go inside and eat?
-Let's go inside.
-Perfect.
Here's the door for you.
I don't think I've ever been here.
Ah. Well, this is your first time.
We're gonna do it together.
[Truman] First blind date.
I'm super nervous.
-Nerves are just excitement on overdrive.
-That's all part of it.
-That's why we certainly need a drink.
-[giggles] Yeah.
I'll grab that for you.
Thank you, sweet gentleman.
Scoot in. [gasps]
-There you go.
-A solid scoot in. Thank you. [giggles]
[bartender] Hey, how you doing?
Here's our cocktail, draft beer
and bottled beer menu.
[Truman] Alrighty.
What are you gonna have?
What are you thinking?
Usually, I just go vodka soda.
What about yourself?
I want to do whiskey.
[chuckles] Get this girl
a whiskey, please.
Get this girl a whiskey. [chuckles]
-Yeah, you look really pretty.
-Oh, why, thank you.
-First blind date for me, so this is good.
-[gasps]
-This is a good experience so far.
-Welcome.
Good. Yay. [chuckles]
It'd be tough if I had to fake anything,
you know?
-But, yeah, you look good.
-Well, thank you.
What do you think is your best Pinot Noir?
You pick your fave.
[bartender] The one from Oregon
is gonna give you not as much dust.
-Then I have another more medium-bodied.
-Do you love dust?
-Alright. We're gonna do the dust.
-We'll take one dusty noir.
I'm, like, allergic to real dust.
-Something different.
-It's a different type of dust.
That type of dust brings about good times.
[chuckles]
-Know why they made that glass like that?
-Tell me.
Louis XIV liked breasts
and so he wanted to grab his cup
like a breast.
So that's why they made--
-It does look like a boob!
-Right?
I love that fun fact.
[both laugh]
-Look at you. You've got great muscles.
-No, it's just the shirt.
It's tight. That's it.
Can I borrow your shirt?
You can have the shirt. Okay?
We can trade.
-I like your rubber band.
-It's for my hair.
I have one in my hair right now.
But it's just that they break, they snap.
I'm bad with bracelets also.
Well, you're wearing a watch.
Yes, to hang out with you.
I want to look my best for you.
-So obviously I can't just be--
-So sweet.
-I love that.
-I'm trying to be honest all the way.
-Amen.
-I don't want to set the bar super high
-and then I come down to here.
-[chuckles] Yeah.
No, I set it here, then I come down
to right here and it's pretty much even.
-Great logic.
-Nothing worse
than people who try to lie on first dates.
The person that you're getting right now
is me.
I'm glad.
Where are you originally from?
I was born and raised here in New Orleans.
-Oh, sweet.
-But I'm Latino, so...
Latino. I love that.
My mom is from Honduras
and my dad's from Guatemala.
I love it.
You've got a good little mix there.
I'm Sicilian on both ends.
-Are you close with your parents?
-Very close.
-I'm actually living with them right now.
-Yeah.
-Me too! I live with my parents.
-Do you?
I... So I bought a house
five blocks down this way.
And it's like a complete renovation.
I've never moved out, so I'm still--
-What?
-Yeah.
-Where are you from?
-I'm originally from New York.
Yeah. Right.
-I just moved out here, like, a year ago.
-Did you?
Did you find similar accents out here?
-Of course not.
-No?
Everybody always tries to say
that we sound like we're from New York.
No-- No. No. Who in the world said that?
[chuckles] Then people lied.
-Cheers.
-Cheers to you.
To boob drinks.
You heard it in New Orleans and it's true.
[laughs] It's true now.
How's your dust?
Oh! Love it.
-[smacks lips]
-Mm. Love the dust.
-Don't sneeze now.
-[giggles]
What do you do?
I'm in the military.
So, I'm in the National Guard
here in Louisiana.
You know, I'm a chiropractor,
so I'm all about health. Yeah.
So I'm a sales exec--
-A sales executive.
-Remix.
[laughs] Try again.
I'm a sales executive
for an international airline.
-Really cool.
-I love that.
-I'm in finance. I do wealth management.
-You're good with numbers.
-I try to be.
-That's, like, your job. [chuckles]
I like numbers. I like numbers.
I am a group fitness instructor.
-Oh. Sweet.
-I teach group fitness classes.
I do enjoy working out.
Underneath all this,
I am, for sure, a tomboy.
A tomboy? Mm.
When I was little,
I used to always tell my dad,
"I'm gonna be the first girl in the NFL."
-I'm five-foot. There's like...
-[laughs]
-Just was not on the cards for me.
-Not in the cards.
Are you super outdoorsy?
Uh, depends on who you ask.
I guess if somebody doesn't hunt,
might think I'm outdoorsy.
I like to hunt.
-So you hunt?
-I do.
Uh...
I'm, like, animal obsessed.
I'm an animal lover to the core.
Um... you know. I'm not mad at it.
I'm not wanting to go
to the hunting camp every single weekend.
If something else is going on,
I'll do something else.
Yeah.
Um...
-What are your passions? What do you do?
-Mm.
Art is my thing.
Anything creative or anything like that.
I've been a makeup artist
for going on eight years now.
-You don't do hair?
-Mm-mm.
You can't fix this?
-I can probably do it. Can you do my hair?
-I do this. No.
Your hair's beautiful.
I wouldn't touch it.
Thank you. I grew it myself.
Long, beautiful, Sicilian hair.
You're beautiful.
Aw. Thank you. You're very handsome, too.
Thank you.
One of my best friends is a makeup artist.
-Yeah?
-She does it for movie sets and stuff.
Yeah, that's what I'm working into.
I got into makeup
because of the art of it.
Um, that's what I always loved.
I don't really care
about the beauty aspect.
When I feel most fulfilled
is when I'm creating...
emotion with my makeup.
-I don't have an artistic bone in my body.
-No?
I didn't make it past finger painting.
-Really?
-No.
Guys, your table's ready
if you'd like to follow me.
-Thanks.
-Okay, perfect.
We're going to the table.
Thanks for the drink.
Thank you.
[waiter] Menus.
-Thanks.
-[waiter] You're welcome.
Thank you.
I am pescatarian.
There you go.
I eat seafood,
but I don't eat dead animals.
-Oh, okay.
-I eat dead fish.
[laughs] I'm about to say,
wouldn't the fish be an animal?
-No.
-Mm?
If I could pet them, I'm not eating them.
Okay. Mm, I understand that.
-Even though you can totally pet a fish.
-I used to pet my pet fish too.
[both laughing]
So it's not even just red meat?
It's no chicken, no turkey?
No dead animals.
-No dead animals?
-Yeah.
[both laughing]
It's just who I am.
So you hunt, obviously.
- Uh, yes.  I-- I-- I enjoy hunting.
-Mm-hmm.
What do you normally hunt?
-Duck and deer would be the main two.
-Okay.
I used to have a pet duck.
I was 100% her mother
and she would sleep in my hand
and I would put her in my neck like this.
She slept in the warmth of my neck.
And she grew up to be a beautiful mallard,
and one day, she flew away.
-[waiter] Are we ready to order?
-I'm gonna do the peacemaker.
Um, and then I'm gonna do
the blackened gulf fish. [laughs]
I'm gonna do the, uh...
cauliflower steak.
[waiter] Cauliflower steak, absolutely.
I think I'm going with the fish,
out of respect for your whole deal.
-Thank you.
-[chuckles]
How old are you?
-Twenty-seven.
-Twenty-seven? You're older than me.
You look so young.
-I get that a lot.
-I thought you were, like, 22 maybe.
-Twenty-two?
-Yeah.
-So how old are you?
-I am 26.
-Mm.
-How old are you?
Take a guess.
-I hate that game.
-I want you to try.
-I-- No.
-Come on, just try.
All right. I'm ten years older.
So...
I have an art brain
and I don't do math too quickly.
Thirty-six.
-Don't be... sad about that.
-Have you ever...
-Do you date men older than you?
-Older? Yeah, I'd rather it.
-Actually? Why?
-Yeah.
They say the maturity levels...
So, me and you
are on the same mature level. [laughs]
Ten years?
It took me ten years to get here?
Ah.
Buen provecho.
-What does that mean? That sounds Italian.
-Bon appétit.
You have a beautiful accent.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Where are you traveling to next?
Or where am I coming with you next?
[giggles]
-I'm just-- I've traveled so many places.
-Yeah.
I haven't found a place
quite like New Orleans, right?
I can go to the bar in New Orleans,
any bar...
-Yeah?
-...sit down next to...
-Whoever.
-...John Doe...
Love him.
-...and kick the shit with him.
-Yeah.
-And he'll kick the shit with me.
-It's so true.
I can feel that you're from here,
because we can shoot the shit.
Like I know
we can have, like, a long conversation.
-Talk about anything.
-It starts from here.
[Ernesto chuckles]
Tell me, your last relationships,
how did they...
-How did they work out?
-My last relationship? Oh.
Well, I haven't been in a relationship
in, like, four years.
Don't do that face.
-[laughs] That was definitely a face, too.
-You were like...
-Four years? Goddamn.
-Yeah.
Four years is a long time,
but I thought it was the one,
and it goddamn crushed me.
I accept it now. It's not a bad thing.
But everybody always tries to ask like,
"How are you single? Why are you single?"
Which implies, like, something's wrong.
Why the hell are you single?
I hate that question.
Especially being a female.
It's so implied that I...
Like, "Why aren't you married?
Why don't you have kids?
What's wrong with you? Are you okay?"
I'm like, "I'm fine.
I-- I like my life. I'm fine."
I think it's important to be by yourself.
That's like the biggest thing I look for.
You know, you've got to be good
on your own before you get someone else.
Me, personally, I want to be with somebody
who, you know, wants to be with me,
-not needs to be with me type of thing.
-Exactly. Exactly.
So tell me about your last relationship.
-Don't roll your eyes.
-[laughs]
No, my last relationship...
ended on a bad note.
Oh, shit.
The problem was
that we moved in right away.
-Mm-mm.
-After a while, it just really exploded.
Did she cheat on you?
We both did some cheating.
Oh, shit.
-Yeah, it was--
-Not good.
I don't say it
as if I'm not ashamed to say it--
-But it is your truth.
-It's the truth.
What do you look for in a man?
A best friend.
Like a partnership.
I've been attracted to conventionally,
like, beautiful men.
Their mind has shown through,
and I've been like,
"Oh, that's not cute at all."
If I cannot have like a...
connection mentally with you or, like,
you can't understand my creative side...
I'm not a trophy wife, to say the least.
Are you on Bumble or anything?
-No.
-You ever do any of that?
Have you done it?
Uh, yeah. But you've got to watch out
on those apps,
'cause sometimes people don't look like--
-Has that happened to you?
-Yes.
Oh, my God. Tell me your story.
How did that happen?
Oh, my God, she was...
I mean, basically, you know...
-really a model, pretty much.
-Yeah.
Straight up. In the pictures.
She showed up
and she was, like, really drugged out.
Was she like,
"Are you ready to do meth together?"
Actually, yeah.
-No way.
-I swear to God.
Because of that, I don't go on dates
from the apps, because--
You never know what meth girl
you're gonna get.
Exactly. You don't know
what you're gonna get.
Do you have a wild side to you?
You're very reserved.
-A wild side? Uh...
-Very...
You can loosen up.
I like...
I guess, um...
You know, when I'm loosening up,
I like going out. I love dancing.
You do?
I'm not too shy. Uh...
-No?
-No.
Yeah, a little liquid courage, it always--
Goes a long way.
-Without a doubt.
-Of course, yeah.
Do you do any, like, charity things?
I've been wanting to do--
-I just did something really cool.
-What did you do?
So Green Park Elementary,
67% of their school is Latino.
So they asked...
I'm chairman of the Hispanic
Young Professionals in New Orleans.
And so two of us went out there
and we had a whole, like,
Junior Achievement Day.
You're representing them.
You have to take care of your community
so that your community
rises with you, right?
Amen. Yeah.
-You have to.
-Absolutely.
Leading kids on the right path.
Goddamn saint.
I'm having dinner with a saint.
-I'm not a saint.
-What?
-Ready to get out of here?
-Let's do it.
[lively music playing]
[Lawrence] It got chilly out here.
Don't split. [gasps] Superstitious.
You didn't split the pole. Good job.
-Is that a--
-Did you do that on purpose?
Yeah, of course.
-No, you didn't. [laughs]
-[laughs]
-Oh, yeah. You're a wonderful person.
-I think you're pretty great, too.
"Pretty" great. Haven't had a compliment
like that in a while.
-Pretty great. [chuckles]
-Pretty great.
-That's a compliment, for sure.
-[chuckles]
-I've had a really good night with you.
-Mm-hmm.
You know, I've really enjoyed meeting you,
hanging out with you, getting to know you.
You know, your outgoing personality.
You're really energetic. I love it.
That's so sweet.
I'm not supposed to give you compliments,
right?
-Not supposed to do the compliments.
-Yes. It's uncomfortable.
Whatever.
[giggles]
Oh, my gosh! [laughs]
I like that confidence.
-You know?
-Went straight for it.
-I knew you were gonna be this guy.
-It is what it is, right?
-I knew it.
-Like I said, I'm straight to the point.
-Right?
-Uh-huh.
Something I would-- I mean,
definitely would love to do again.
-Yeah?
-I guess we'll just see what's going on.
I don't know. I feel like maybe you're...
Would you ever even get my art side?
-Your art side?
-I don't know if you would. Yeah.
I feel like you're so sweet.
But I feel like it would be so hard
for you to open up to me.
Or, like, get into in-depth conversations
with my mind.
I'm a weird girl.
I don't know if you can handle that.
My weird side.
-It's a fair assumption, I think.
-Yeah.
I am so fucking weird.
No, that's totally fair.
I think that's just something
that I guess we'd have to see with time.
I think you're very sweet and very social.
Well, Heather, I appreciate it.
I've had a very good time.
I'm glad you've talked to me,
and it was good hanging out with you,
and I wish you the best of luck
in your future.
Thank you so much, Truman.
Thank you.
Have a good night. Thank you so much.
-Are you gonna be safe getting home?
-I will. I promise.
-Are you sure? Okay.
-I totally promise.
-[chuckles] Bye, Truman.
-Bye.
Come on.
[giggles]
-[Deahvon] Come here, you.
-[kisses]
I'm gonna get him to come.
I'll go get him.
-Let's see what you got.
-Come here, baby.
[kisses]
Come here.
Oh, my God, yay.
Hey, buddy.
-[Deahvon] Okay, so you--
-Hello.
Hi.
[kisses]
Oh, he's so handsome.
He's perfect.
He's amazing. Do you want to pet him?
-No.
-He doesn't want you to pet him.
[chuckles] So you're just out here
petting stray cats?
-That's what it is? [chuckles]
-Yeah. Bye. Love you.
-I don't... [chuckles]
-You didn't like that?
-No, that was great.
-That's a goddamn highlight.
I don't know
what in the hell you just did, but...
I don't know what kind of demon cat lady
you are, but all right.
-Demon cat lady?
-[laughs]
I think you have...
You might have some demons,
'cause he did not want to come by you.
[indistinct chatter]
-Want me to scoot it in?
-Yeah. [giggles]
-Boom.
-[gasps] Perfect.
So do tell, for you...
What's a deal-breaker for you?
-A deal-breaker?
-With a guy. What's a deal-breaker?
Hates animals.
Hates animals. Oh, okay.
-That's a deal-breaker.
-Do you hate animals?
-Of course not.
-Good.
-What's your deal-breaker?
-[sighs, tutting]
All right, um...
-Somebody who complains a lot.
-Mm.
Like a real negative person.
That's a deal-breaker
in just a human being to be around.
-It's just like... It's draining.
-Yeah.
You choose happiness.
Exactly. So...
It's up to you. Oh, I love that.
Yours was way deeper. I'm like, "Animals."
You're like,
"Let me get a little more psychological."
-I'm just saying--
-That was a good answer.
Do you ever watch Planet Earth?
I do. The voice-over guy...
-David Attenborough.
-That's his name!
Oh, my God! You're a fan.
-He's the shit.
-He's your idol.
-He is the shit.
What do you like?
I've been watching Peaky Blinders.
-What? That's my favorite show.
-You like it?
-No fucking way! Yay!
-Fucking way.
-So Season Five just came out, right?
-Yeah, I just started it.
I love that. I like--
I've never met any girl
that liked that show.
-Really?
-I mean, like...
-It's such a good show.
-Yeah.
[in British accent]
Fuckin' Peaky Blinders.
-No? Okay.
-Yeah. [laughs]
-Yeah. Your scratchy voice? Girl, get it.
-I don't know. Get it. [chuckles]
-Cheers to that.
-Drink our whiskey to that.
-Okay. [laughs]
-She's got a whiskey.
Wait, so you, in your past relationship,
like the last one,
-you said you both cheated though.
-Mm-hmm.
When you said it, I was like, "Oh,
my gosh, is that like a casual thing?"
Hell, no. I ain't got time for that shit.
'Cause I am not... I am like a...
I... I have my boundaries.
-Of course.
-Trust issues from my past.
I'm not gonna lie.
It definitely was a trigger for me.
That's why I'd rather say it upfront.
I fucked up.
So you don't condone cheating?
Like, you want to be
in a monogamous relationship?
Yes. Because it doesn't hurt just you.
It hurts that person.
It hurts that person and their friends.
It hurts the person that supports them.
That temporary fix I was looking for,
all it did was just burn everything
to the ground.
I fucked it up. I dropped the ball.
-I love that you're owning it.
-I did something fucking terrible.
-Yeah.
-And I don't want any of that.
Never again in my life.
Tell me about the ups and downs
of your relationships
that you went through.
So...
my past relationship four years ago
was the one I lost my virginity to,
so, like, that was...
'Cause I had it for so long and it was
something very special to me, that...
Losing that was a big part of my identity.
And then, right after that...
he just left.
So that kind of stole a piece of me,
and it kind of made me...
It made me less naive.
But it also made me more guarded
and, like, when my guard's up, I...
usually keep it up. [chuckles]
-Are you ready to get out of here?
-Are you?
I am. Let's go.
Maybe we could get these to go.
These beautiful little pink drinks.
Like, I loved our whole conversation.
I loved learning about everything
about you. Are you ready?
-Let's go.
-Let's go!
-[Montrell] Had a great time.
-[Heather] It was fun. See you next time.
[laughing]
Did you have fun?
-I did.
-Yeah.
-I had a lot of fun.
-Me too.
[chuckling] Oh, my God.
[sighs]
What was your favorite part?
-You.
-Oh, yeah?
I didn't expect this.
-No?
-No, not at all.
What did you expect?
I don't know.
-Did you enjoy yourself tonight?
-I did.
You're so fun. You're so easy to talk to.
I like that you can dish it back, too.
-Of course I can.
-That's fun.
Just along for the ride.
Same here.
How fun.
Your first date didn't go awry.
-You didn't even know--
-I swear, I mean, I'm still here.
Maybe you should do more dates
where you didn't expect...
This is the first blind date, like, ever,
so it's like, yeah...
It's definitely a good experience.
I mean, it's definitely gone right,
so that's good.
-Well, yay, I'm glad.
-Yeah. Yeah.
I adored this.
Thank you so much for all the stories
and all the fun.
-Of course.
-I had so much fun with you.
-Are we gonna do it again?
-We're gonna do it again.
-We're gonna have a lot of fun.
-We are.
I can't wait to style your curly hair.
You're gonna style it up?
-I'm gonna style your curly hair.
-You do a shoot?
Yeah. I love it.
I'm down.
Whenever you want.
We'll work it out.
[chuckles]
So cute.
And definitely very handsome.
[chuckles]
-Stop staring.
-For a kiss?
Yeah?
You've been wanting to.
Oh, my God.
You're a good kisser.
-Am I?
-Mm-hmm.
Why do you say that?
'Cause it was a good kiss. [laughs]
[chuckles]
Oh, my... [laughs]
Bye. [chuckles]
Hopefully see you soon.
-I know.
-All right.
All right.
Bye.
[indistinct chatter]
[big band music playing]
[big band music continues]
Hey!
Hello, handsome.
[Ernesto]
Good to see you. You look beautiful.
A band!
-Let's dance.
[big band music playing]
[Heather laughing]
[Heather] Do you wanna go
grab some drinks?
[Ernesto chuckles] Of course.
Might as well do it.
-[Heather] Might as well.
-We're in New Orleans, right?
[big band music playing]